AAA Arbitration in the Schools Records 6309
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AAA Arbitration in the Schools Records
1969-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Arbitration Association (AAA)
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
6309
21 cubic feet
21 linear ft.
Contract awards.
7130119
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
N. Wolski, September 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; American Arbitration Association.
7130119
- Summary and Awards, no.100 (1969). Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.1 (1970:Mar.) - v.7 (1970:Sep.). (Box 1)
  - American Arbitration Association Summary and Awards #100 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association: Arbitration in the Schools., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools No. 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 3, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 4, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 5, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 6, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 7, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.8 (1970:Oct.) - v.15 (1971:May). (Box 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 8, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 9 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 10, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 12, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 13, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 14, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 15, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.16 (1971:June) - v.25 (1972:March). (Box 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 16, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 17, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 18, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 19, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 20, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 21, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 22`, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 23, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 24, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 25, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.26 (1972:March) - v.34 (1972:Dec.). (Box 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 26, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 27, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 28, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 29, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 30, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 31, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 32, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 33, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 34, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.35 (1973:Jan.) - v.46 (1973:Dec.). (Box 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 35, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 36, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 37, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 38, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 39, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 40, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 41, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 42, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 43, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 44, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 45, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 46, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.47 (1974:Jan.) - v.57 (1974:Nov.). (Box 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 47, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 48, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 49, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 50, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 51, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 52, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 53, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 54, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 55, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 56, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 57, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.58 (1974:Dec.) - v.67 (1975:Sep.). (Box 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 58, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 59, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 60, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 61, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 62, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 63, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 65, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 64, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 66, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in the Schools No. 67, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.68 (1975:Sep.) - v.78 (1976:Aug.). (Box 8)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. Oct. 1975 No. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. Oct. 1975 No.69 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. Oct. 1975 No. 70 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 71 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 72 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 73 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 74 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 75 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 76 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 77 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 78 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.79 (1976:Sep.) - v.88 (1977:Aug.). (Box 9)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 79 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 80 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 81 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 82 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 83 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1976 No. 84 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1977 No. 85 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1977 No. 86 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1977 No. 87 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. 1977 No. 88 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.90 - v.99. (Box 10)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 90 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 91 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 92 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 93 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 94 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 95 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 96 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 97 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - American Arbitration Association Arbitration in the Schools Awards & Fact-finding Recommendations. No. 98 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Economics - Statistics - Bibliography (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.100 - v.110. (Box 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. Vol. 100 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 101 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 102 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 103 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 104 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 105 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 106 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 107 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 108 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 110 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 109 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.112 - v.123. (Box 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 112 (1-22) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 113 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 114 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 115 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 116 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Economic Planning - US (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 118 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 119 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 120 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 121 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 122 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 123 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.124 - v.137. (Box 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 124 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 125 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 126 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 127 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 128 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 128 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 130 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 131 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 132 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 133 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 134 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 135 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 136 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 137 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.138 - v.152. (Box 14)
  - AAA in schools vol 138 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 139 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 140 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 141 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 142 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 143 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 144 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 145 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 146 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 147 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 148 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 149 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 150 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 151 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 152 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.153 - v.168. (Box 15)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 153 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 154 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 155 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 156 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 157 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 158 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 159 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 160 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 161 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 162 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 163 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 164 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 165 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 166 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 167 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 168 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.169 - v.183. (Box 16)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 169 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 170 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 171 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 172 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 173 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 174 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 175 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 176 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 177 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 178 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 179 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 180 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 181 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 182 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 183 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.184 - v.198. (Box 17)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 184 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 185 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 186 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 187 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 188 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 190 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 189 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 191 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 192 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 193 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 194 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 195 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 196 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 197 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 198 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.199 - v.230. (Box 18)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 199 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 201 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 202 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 203 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 204 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 205 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 206 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 207 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 208 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 209 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 210 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 218 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 220 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 227 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 228 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 229 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 230 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.231 - v.246. (Box 19)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 231 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 232 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 233 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 234 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 235 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 236 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 237 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 238 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 239 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 240 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 241 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 242 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 243 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 244 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 245 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 246 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.247 - v.266. (Box 20)
  - C69S98 Collective Agreements - Sweden (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 248 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 249 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 250 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 251 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 252 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 254 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 255 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 256 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 257 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 258 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 259 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 261 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 262 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 263 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 264 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 265 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Awards and Fact-Finding Recommendations, v.267 - v.276. (Box 21)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 267 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 268 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 269 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 270 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 271 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 272 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 273 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 274 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 275 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - AAA Arbitration in schools vol. 276 (Box 21, Folder 10)